Guide to the Dan Nimrod papers, 1938-2002 MS2192
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Publications, 1959-2002; MS2192 Series 8; 5 Linear feet
  - Jimmy Carter flunks history, 09/24/1990 (Box 15, Folder 111)
  - "Death to the Jews", 10/18/1990 (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Dear Sir-Madam, 12/1990 (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Dear Elyakim, 11/11/1990 (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - UN members hold secret talks on conference with Palestinians, 12/1990 (Box 15, Folder 115)
  - Why Israel should hold the West Bank: Why Canadians should agree, 12/19/1990 (Box 15, Folder 116)
  - Pan-Arab goal, 12/1990 (Box 15, Folder 117)
  - The myth of linkage: Why the Gulf crisis is unrelated to the Palestinian issue, 12/1990 (Box 15, Folder 118)
  - The Editor, The Gazette, 01/07/1991 (Box 15, Folder 119)
  - Canada applies double standard on human rights for Israel, 01/23/1991 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - Israel's political dogma on Jordan, 02/20/1991 (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - The Gazette's Management & Editorial Staff, 02/18/1991 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Fraser, Joan, Editorial Page Editor, The Gazette, 02/07/1991 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Walker, J.R., Deputy Managing Editor/Ombudsman, 02/08/1991 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - The real linkage, 03/01/1991 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Dear Friends Letter, 03/14/1991 (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Geography & Security, by George, 03/31/1991 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Israel won't give in on West Bank, 04/01/1991 (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - Palestinians can't have two and a half states, 04/09/1991 (Box 15, Folder 129)
  - Dear Reader, 04/17/1991 (Box 15, Folder 130)
  - Jinsa - West Bank Ideal for 'smart weapons', 04/19/1991 (Box 15, Folder 131)
  - Israel after the Gulf War, 05/01/1991 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - The real impediment, 05/25/1991 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Arab stand on settlements reveals their true nature, 07/11/1991 (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - Supplement to the Chairman's Report of Dr. Reuben R. Hecht, 05/14/1991 (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - The PLO in diplomatic darkness, 05/01/1991 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - The Honorable George Bush, 05/02/1991 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - Israel's learned to be wary, 05/11/1991 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - A threat to democracy is a threat to Zionism, 06/01/1991 (Box 15, Folder 139)
  - Walker, J.R., Deputy Managing Editor/ Ombudsman, 06/19/1991 (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - Memorandum for the leadership and active members of the Cdn Jewish community & other concerned parties abroad, 07/01/1991 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - Addendum to the ten-page memorandum of July 2, 1991, for the leadership and active ..., 07/01/1991 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - Nisan, Mordechai, 08/28/1991 (Box 15, Folder 143)
  - To the editor: German consul replies, 10/02/1991 (Box 15, Folder 144)
  - Balgur, Rafael, 10/31/1991 (Box 15, Folder 145)
  - Middle East peace talks - UN's 'Zionism is racism' must go as first step, 11/05/1991 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  - Israel moves to strengthen ties with South Africa, 12/01/1991 (Box 15, Folder 147)
  - From the Archives - Article in Hebrew, 12/11/1991 (Box 15, Folder 148)
  - Is Israel confronted with a new Gulf coalition?, 01/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 149)
  - The art of negotiating an Arab-Israeli peace, 01/08/1992 (Box 15, Folder 150)
  - Gaining the room to negotiate, 01/13/1992 (Box 15, Folder 151)
  - Zionism-racism resolution repeal doesn't cleanse UN, 01/22/1992 (Box 15, Folder 152)
  - United Nations anti-Semitic stamp targets the young, 02/05/1992 (Box 15, Folder 153)
  - UN's double standard in Mid-East smells to high heaven + German translation, 02/26/1992 (Box 15, Folder 154)
  - Stamp inconsistent with UN rule, but UN won't act, 03/04/1992 (Box 15, Folder 155)
  - Labour Party policy weakens Israel's negotiators, 03/18/1992 (Box 15, Folder 156)
  - Round II of "The Richler Affair", 03/30/1992 (Box 15, Folder 157)
  - Palestinian Women under occupation, 04/1992 ca. (Box 15, Folder 158)
  - Wannsee memorial - remembering for the future, 04/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 159)
  - Does the solution for "Palestinian" Arab refugees rest on repatriation or resettlement?, 05/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 160)
  - The Jewish Refugees, 05/08/1992 (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - Refugees for all seasons, 05/23/1992 (Box 15, Folder 162)
  - Thoughts on European participation in Middle East, 06/19/1992 (Box 15, Folder 163)
  - Selected articles - indexed, 06/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 164)
  - Kirk, David, 06/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 165)
  - Hafez Assad is wrong: U.S. saturates Arabs with arms, 06/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 166)
  - No time for Jewish claims, 06/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Greenfield, Richard, 07/15/1992 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Hanan Ashrawi: The face behind the mask, 07/22/1992 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Palestinian Arab solution to refugee resettlement, 08/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - The 'Land for Peace' Concept: In Perspective, 08/14/1992 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Kirk, David, 08/26/1992 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - The Target: The German Chancellor - A Jewish Underground in the 1950s, 09/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - The case of the Palestinian Arab refugee problem - Part I, 09/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Nimrod, Dan, 09/03/1992 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - An open letter to Prime Minister Rabin, 09/30/1992 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Nimrod, Dan, 10/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Members of the 13th Knesset, 10/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Nativ - A Journal of politics and the arts, 11/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Tagar' means challenge, for defenders of the Jewish interest, 11/04/1992 (Box 15, Folder 180)
  - From the battle of El Alamein to the valour and the horror (series 1 to 9), 12/01/1992 (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Sontag, Eric, 12/03/1992 (Box 15, Folder 182)
  - CJC still can't see the problem, 01/01/1993 (Box 15, Folder 183)
  - Israel's leftists meddle in South Africa's internal affairs, 01/01/1993 (Box 15, Folder 184)
  - Germany's extreme hate groups now number 76, 01/27/1993 (Box 15, Folder 185)
  - Zion liberated - Book Review, 02/01/1993 (Box 15, Folder 186)
  - Israel & South Africa (series of 6 articles), 02/24/1993 (Box 15, Folder 187)
  - UN Hypocrisy, 03/01/1993 (Box 15, Folder 188)
  - Modell, Sol, 03/12/1993 (Box 15, Folder 189)
  - What kind of peace is over the rainbow?, 05/01/1993 (Box 15, Folder 190)
  - A German perspective - Wannsee Memorial - Remembering for the future, 05/01/1993 (Box 15, Folder 191)
  - Abandonment of Jews by institutions not limited to the Diaspora, 05/05/1993 (Box 15, Folder 192)
  - Shamir protest fizzles; NDP youth leader admits mistake, 07/01/1993 (Box 15, Folder 193)
  - Labour's immunity from criticism is not a God-given right, 07/01/1993 (Box 15, Folder 194)
  - Khoury, Claude, Mideast Mirror, 07/29/1993 (Box 15, Folder 195)
  - When it comes to Israel's security, nobody knows more than Yitzhak Rabin. Nobody, 08/1993 (Box 15, Folder 196)
  - Mainstream American Jewish groups break with Rabin over abandonment of Jewish lands, 09/1993 (Box 15, Folder 197)
  - Interview with Dan Nimrod for the McGill Daily - A realistic perspective about the Israel-PLO Washington accord, 10/01/1993 (Box 15, Folder 198)
  - Goldfoot, Stanley, Temple Mount Foundation, 10/20/1993 (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - Timetable for Israel-PLO accord, 11/26/1993 (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - Peres & Beilin seeking asylum in Norway (Hebrew), 01/01/1994 (Box 15, Folder 201)
  - More revelations about the Iran-Contra affair, 02/01/1994 (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - Israeli Suicide Drive (Parts 1 to 15) - The Arab-Israel Conflict without bias or prejudice (Vol. II) Parts 23 to 30, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - Greenberg, Jack, 02/24/1994 (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - The unutterable ironies of Israel's growing insecurity, 03/01/1994 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - The Kafka parable for our time, 03/01/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 1)
  - To our people of Israel, 03/01/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 2)
  - Hebron and the dialectic of the Israeli-Arab struggle, 03/01/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 3)
  - Second Hebron Massacre - Hebron revisited, 03/01/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 4)
  - Conflict resolution through population transfer - Parts 1 to 5, 04/01/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 5)
  - Generals make major mistakes, 06/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 6)
  - The Stephen Scheinberg dossier, 06/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 7)
  - Shechter, Reuben, Director Zionist Organization of America, 08/10/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 8)
  - A nation collaborating in its own demise, 08/01/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 9)
  - Israeli left's problem: rightist conscientious objectors, 09/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 10)
  - Rabin on the 'commonality of Jewish fate' in Israel and the Diaspora - as one is killed, so is the other, Part 1 & 2, 09/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 11)
  - Autonomy for Israeli Arab citizens?, 09/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 12)
  - Torczyner, Jacques, 09/16/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 13)
  - Nimrod, Dan, 10/11/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 14)
  - Published articles re: Mordecai Richler, 10/12/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 15)
  - Even, Ephraim, Editor Ha-Umma, 10/27/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 16)
  - The tendency to perceive oneself in the image of anti-semitic sterotypes (parts 1 & 2), 11/01/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 17)
  - Peace Prize Travesty (Parts 1 to 12), 12/01/1994 (Box 16A, Folder 18)
  - Bad trip to a dead end where Richler has chosen to live, 02/01/1995 (Box 16A, Folder 19)
  - Demophrenia: Israel and the malaise of democracy, 03/01/1995 (Box 16A, Folder 20)
  - The Arab-Israel conflict without bias or prejudice (Parts 1 - 12), 04/01/1995 (Box 16A, Folder 21)
  - The Arab-Israel conflict without bias or prejudice (Parts 23-27), 06/01/1995 (Box 16A, Folder 22)
  - Nimrod, Dan, 07/30/1995 (Box 16A, Folder 23)
  - Blueprint Canada for the 21st century, 10/01/1995 (Box 16A, Folder 24)
  - Filling in the blanks in Rabin's Eulogies (1), 12/01/1995 (Box 16A, Folder 25)
  - The Moment of Truth (Part I), 12/13/1995 (Box 16A, Folder 26)
  - The Moment of Truth (Part II) - Filling in the blanks in Rabin's eulogies, 01/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 27)
  - The Moment of Truth (Part III) - Filling in the blanks in Rabin's eulogies, 02/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 28)
  - Jews and Blacks: Spare us the comparison, 03/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 29)
  - The Peace of the Grave, 03/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 30)
  - The "Shalom Haverim" Concept, 04/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 31)
  - Reshuffling the deck for Israel's May 29th election (parts 1 to 7), 05/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 32)
  - An open letter to Leah Rabin (1 to 6), 06/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 33)
  - Likud victory has given the Jewish state a new lease on life, 06/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 34)
  - When gay power targets the youth of the nation it is time to draw the line, 07/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 35)
  - Suburban to appeal Quebec Press Council decision, 07/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 36)
  - An Israeli address to the nations of the world, 07/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 37)
  - The Paul Druzin dossier (a case history of "gay" intolerance for freedom of expression), 07/25/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 38)
  - Listing of Canadian, American and Overseas Publications containing writings by Dan Nimrod, 08/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 39)
  - Who is the oppressor in the Middle East? Who is killing peace?, 10/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 40)
  - Drissman, Michael re: Appeal to the National Camp - part I, 11/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 41)
  - From Washington to Berlin: Investing in the future, 12/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 42)
  - Homosexualists rehash old news just to keep the pot boiling, 12/01/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 43)
  - Modell, Sol re: Appeal to the National Camp - part II, 12/20/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 44)
  - The John Dirlik versus Dan Nimrod Dossier - (A case history of an Arab attempt to invert the truth on the Arab-Israel Conflict), 12/31/1996 (Box 16A, Folder 45)
  - German Anti-Semitism: U.K. Minister hit with Nazi-like slur, 02/01/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 46)
  - Haddad, Heskel M., 02/04/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 47)
  - Libman, Robert & Ben-Dat, Mordechai, 02/17/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 48)
  - Questions arising from the Oslo Accords, 03/01/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 49)
  - The Peace Process - Guest Editorial, 03/13/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 50)
  - Old blood libel levelled at Israel by PA, 03/17/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 51)
  - Wijnen, Janice, 03/31/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 52)
  - The Gazette on Israel, 04/01/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 53)
  - Jewish Rights vs. Arab Claims, 04/01/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 54)
  - Exploring self-destructive pattern of behaviour (parts 1 to 7), 05/01/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 55)
  - Reflections - Holocaust Desecration, 05/02/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 56)
  - More reactions to Janice Wijnen's letters of protest, 05/26/1997-06/05/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 57)
  - McCormick, Christie, Editor, The Suburban, 05/23/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 58)
  - Parker, Aida, 07/18/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 59)
  - Biographical Highlights - Dr. Franklin H. Littell, 08/01/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 60)
  - Eretz Yisrael - Historical Palestine Series Israel's mistakes are never forgiven, 12/01/1997 (Box 16A, Folder 61)
  - Bishop's remarks on Palestinians outrage Israeli, 12/28/1997 (Box 16B, Folder 62)
  - Dear Reader, 01/05/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 63)
  - Testimony and Warning - Preface, 03/01/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 64)
  - Reflections on Israel's 50th anniversary, 05/01/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 65)
  - At Last, Zion: Israel and the fate of the Jews, 05/11/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 66)
  - Address by Dan Nimrod at a private gathering on July 5, 1998, on the occasion of his 75th birthday, 07/01/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 67)
  - A tribute to Dan Nimrod on his 75th birthday, 07/01/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 68)
  - Nimrod, Dan, 07/27/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 69)
  - Text of a letter to an Israeli friend, 08/19/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 70)
  - The Saga of Ben Weider: Humanitarianism without frontiers, 08/01/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 71)
  - The betrayal of the State by the Israeli right, 11/01/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 72)
  - Towards a Commission for National Salvation - Jews are fiddling while Jerusalem burns, 12/01/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 73)
  - Tamir, Peleg, Chairman, Jabotinsky Institute in Israel, 12/04/1998 (Box 16B, Folder 74)
  - Text of Circular Letter, 01/18/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 75)
  - The Clinton Resignation Option, 01/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 76)
  - The Jewish State: The next fifty years, 02/01/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 77)
  - A show fit for an emperor, 04/29/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 78)
  - Israel's 51st Independence Day: The end of an era or a new beginning?, 05/31/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 79)
  - Excerpts from a letter to the Board Members of the Toronto Zionist Council, 07/20/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 80)
  - Professor Edward Said revisited, 09/01/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 81)
  - The deconstruction of Said, 09/01/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 82)
  - New Millennium, new challenges, 09/03/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 83)
  - Ben-Dat, Mordechai, Editor, The Canadian Jewish News, 09/03/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 84)
  - A U.S. President insists: Israel must have the Golan, 09/03/1999 (Box 16B, Folder 85)
  - Dawn Publications Catalogue 2000 - Views rarely seen in the media, 01/01/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 86)
  - Israel's New Quislings - Volumes 1 & 2, 01/01/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 87)
  - The Price of Withdrawal, 01/01/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 88)
  - The song of the Biryonim, 04/01/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 89)
  - Israel's New Quislings - Volume Two, 02/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 90)
  - Reader's reactions to the George Washington University Press release, 04/20/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 91)
  - Current Affairs File - Political Digest Series, 05/01/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 92)
  - Shapiro, Jay, 06/08/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 93)
  - Responding to 'Peace Now' Arguments - Compromise not synonymous with surrender, 08/04/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 94)
  - The rejection of Peres: A humiliating defeat for Barak and Oslo - Parts 1,2,3, 08/23/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 95)
  - Address at George Washington University, 11/29/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 96)
  - Weider, Ben - Special Edition, 09/01/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 97)
  - G.W.U. - Celebrating the Acquisition of the D. Nimrod Collection of Reference books, Dawn archives and Personal Papers, 01/01/2001 (Box 16B, Folder 98)
  - Carpi, Daniel, 02/26/2000 (Box 16B, Folder 99)
  - Dear Friends Letter, 02/09/2001 (Box 16B, Folder 100)
  - Dear Friend Letter, 04/19/2001 (Box 16C, Folder 101)
  - Medical Bulletin, 07/10/2001 (Box 16C, Folder 102)
  - A letter to an American friend, 09/14/2001 (Box 16C, Folder 103)
  - Israel Today & Always: To whom does it belong?, 02/03/2002 (Box 16C, Folder 104)
  - Ha'etzni, Elyakim, 02/21/2002 (Box 16C, Folder 105)
  - President George Bush - Action Alert, 03/08/2002 (Box 16C, Folder 106)
  - The Arab-Israeli Conflict from a Jewish Perspective - An unfinished political digest by Dan Nimrod, 06/2002 (Box 16C, Folder 107)
  - An Appeal for Jewish Solidarity - Americans for Undivided Israel (Box 16C, Folder 108)
  - The Arab-Israel conflict without bias or prejudice (parts X to XV) (Box 16C, Folder 109)
  - B.C.'s leadership '92 conference hotbed for racist hatemongers - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 110)
  - B'nai B'rith chairman remains unrepentant - his regrets are self-serving - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 111)
  - A black day for Canadian Jewry - The demise of a leadership - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 112)
  - Can Israel be defended by extoling the opposition? - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 113)
  - Concessions made by the opposition weaken the Government's negotiating stance - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 114)
  - Response to 'detention center' charge - Democracy doesn't have all the answers - Eidelberg, Paul (Box 16C, Folder 115)
  - Hanan Ashrawi: The "New Face" for the "New Palestinian" - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 116)
  - Human Rights Group squashes Pro-Israel report - Wolf, Gary (Box 16C, Folder 117)
  - Israel' contributions to coalition - Near East Report (Box 16C, Folder 118)
  - Israel's foreign ministry's faulty map reflects policies of new Labour government - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 119)
  - Jews welcoming Mandela: A question of tactics and principle - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 120)
  - Monitoring the German Scene - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 121)
  - The Palestinian Labyrinth - A Way Out - Aumann, Moshe (Box 16C, Folder 122)
  - Ottawa peace talks will focus exclusively on Palestinian Arab refugees but Arab claims cannot be divorced from Jewish claims - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 123)
  - The Political Geography of Palestine: a History and Definition - Rolef, Susan Hattis (Box 16C, Folder 124)
  - The Proclamation issued by the Irgun Zvai Leumi (Box 16C, Folder 125)
  - A Richler profile for the next generation - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 126)
  - Profile of an unholy alliance - Richler's solid ground on slippery ice - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 127)
  - Racism and Anti-Semitism in Canada - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 128)
  - The Abandonment of Jews by their institutions not limited to the Diaspora - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 129)
  - Terrorism - and the lie about Palestine - Zionist Action Detroit (Box 16C, Folder 130)
  - Time for Middle East Peace? - Thomas, Cal (Box 16C, Folder 131)
  - U.N. Double Standard smells to high heaven! - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 132)
  - Begin's declaration of independence - U.S.-Israel rift in Perspective - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 133)
  - Sadat's Strategy - What can we do? - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 134)
  - Inverting the truth - Nimrod, Dan (Box 16C, Folder 135)
  - Miscellaneous Jewish Materials - Various documents (Box 16C, Folder 136)
  - The Savage Kinship a chronology of the use of violence for political ends in Arab countries, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Oslo B the establishment of a Palestinian State by the Government of Israel (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The Canadian Jewish Herald, 09/1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - The Canadian Jewish Herald, 04/1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The Canadian Jewish Herald, 11/1978 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - International Conference: Jordan is Palestine, 1983-1985; Series 8 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Content in this folder relate to the International Conference Jordan is Palestine
    Resume of the Relevant Deliberations and Resolutions on Crucial Issues COnfronting the J.I.P. Campaign; The Peace Process 1985 Political Analysis, Policy Outline Propositions for Resolutions.
  - Dawn Collector's Library, 1985; Series 8 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Content in this folder relate to the Dawn Collector's Library
    The 'Plo' Terrorism and National Security; Views of the Middle East Conflict Rarely Seen in the Media; The First Ten Years of UN Stand on Zionism; Polemical Documents Series Abba Eban Reconsidered.
  - Dawn's Continuous Information Policy Guide, 1986-1988; Series 8 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Content in this folder relate to Dawn's Continuous Information Policy Guide
    History in the Making; The Jewish "Jihad" Against Kahane; Off the Record Confidentially Speaking; The Litmus Test of Democracy in Israel.
  - Dawn's Continuous Information Policy Guide, 1989-1996; Series 8 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Auschwitz 1989 The Second Encounter; Postmortem of a Failed Uprising the Jerusalem Post in Test of Time; The Stephen Scheinberg Dossier; history in the Making; The Paul Druzin Dossier.
  - Dawn's Continuous Information Policy Guide, 1997-1999; Series 8 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Israel's Mistakes are Never Forgiven: Amidst a Sea of Haterd and Hypocrisy it is a Miracle That Israel is Still Alive; Israel's 51st Independence Day: The End of an Era or a New Beginning? Historical Voluntary Withdrawal of the State of Israel From the Land of Israel.
  - Dawn's Continuous Policy Guide, 2000; Series 8 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Israels' New Quislings; Current Affairs File.
- Book Reviews and Promotional Materials, 1977-2002; MS2192 Series 9; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains book reviews by Nimrod and by others about Dawn Publishing's works. It also contains material, mostly letters, related to Nimrod's activities promoting his publications. The material dates from 1977-2002.
  - Aba Eban Reconsidered - by Rafael Medoff - Review, 1985 (Box 16C, Folder 137)
  - American Middle East Foreign Policy: A Political Reevaluation - Reviews, 1983-1984 (Box 16C, Folder 138)
  - Axis of Anti-Semitism - by Daniel Carpi - Review, 1985 (Box 16C, Folder 139)
  - Canadian Jewish Herald - Reviews and Reactions (Box 16C, Folder 140)
  - Jewish Rights as Opposed to Arab Claims - Review, 06/1984 (Box 16C, Folder 141)
  - Lucy Dawidowicz and the Holocaust Industry & In Memory of Vilma, 01/21/1985-04/1985 (Box 16C, Folder 142)
  - No solution to the Palestinian Problem - by Shmuel Katz - Review, 1985 (Box 16C, Folder 143)
  - Palestine Past & Present - 5 New Dawn Publications - Review, 1985 (Box 16C, Folder 144)
  - Peace Now - by Dan Nimrod - Readers comments, 06/1984-1985 (Box 16C, Folder 145)
  - Peace Now - by Dan Nimrod - Reviews & reactions, 06/1984-1985 (Box 16C, Folder 146)
  - Peace Now - by Dan Nimrod - Reviews, 07/04/1984-12/1985 (Box 16D, Folder 147)
  - Role of Arab Political Culture & History in the Conflict with Israel - by Arnold Soloway - Review, 1985 (Box 16D, Folder 148)
  - Sadat's Strategy - by Paul Eidelberg - Reviews & reactions, 05/16/1979-03/03/1986 (Box 16D, Folder 149)
  - Sadat's Strategy - by Paul Eidelberg - Promotion of, 11/18/1979-04/1980 (Box 16D, Folder 150)
  - Terrorism vs. Democracy - 2 essays by Paul Johnson & George Schultz - Review, 1986 (Box 16D, Folder 151)
  - The Case of Israel's Jewish Underground - by Paul Eidelberg - Review, 1985 (Box 16D, Folder 152)
  - The first 10 years of UN stand on Zionism - Review, 1985 (Box 16D, Folder 153)
  - The Peace Process 1985: Political Analysis, Policy Outline, Propositions for Resolutions - Review (Box 16D, Folder 154)
  - Toward a new American Middle-East Policy - by Peter Goldman - Review, 1985 (Box 16D, Folder 155)
  - Views of the Middle East Conflict rarely seen in the media - Edited by Dan Nimrod - Review, 1985 (Box 16D, Folder 156)